<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><root><rating type="float">4.2</rating><votes type="str">448</votes><title type="str">The Bathroom Joke</title><url type="str">http://www.greatcleanjokes.com/31/long-joke/</url><content type="str">Three engineers and three accountants are traveling       by train to a conference.At the station, the three accountants each  buy       tickets and watch as the three engineers buy only a single ticket.”How are three people going to travel on only       one ticket?” asks an accountant.”Watch and you’ll see,” answers an       engineer. All of them board the train.The accountants take their respective seats  but all       three engineers cram into a restroom and close the door behind  them.Shortly after the train has departed, the  conductor       comes around collecting tickets. He knocks on the restroom door  and says,       “Ticket, please.”The door opens just a crack and a single arm  emerges       with a ticket in hand. The conductor takes it and moves on.The accountants saw this and agreed it was  a       clever idea.So after the conference, the accountants  decide to       copy the engineers on the return trip and save some money .When they get to the station they buy a  single ticket       for the return trip.To their astonishment, the engineers don’t  buy a       ticket at all.”How are you going to travel without a       ticket?” says one perplexed accountant.”Watch and you’ll see,” answers an       engineer.When they board the train the three  accountants cram       into a restroom and the three engineers cram into another one  nearby. The       train departs.Shortly afterward, one of the engineers  leaves his       restroom and walks over to the restroom where the accountants are  hiding.He knocks on the door and says, “Ticket,       please.”</content><comments_count type="str">10</comments_count><id type="str">455</id><categories type="list"><item type="dict"><subcategory_id type="str">171</subcategory_id><category_id type="str">124</category_id><subcategory_name type="str">Long Jokes</subcategory_name><category_name type="str">Other Joke Types</category_name></item><item type="dict"><subcategory_id type="str">199</subcategory_id><category_id type="str">133</category_id><subcategory_name type="str">Clever Jokes</subcategory_name><category_name type="str">Witty Jokes</category_name></item></categories></root>